My doc told me to half my test dose
because my estrogen was too high. Now
I'm feeling like garbage. What should I
do? Find a new doctor. That's easy.
I mean, I can't give you personal
advice. But I mean, if someone gave you
the advice to jump off a cliff, I'd say
that's a bad idea. um having your test
dose, even if your test dose was too
high, unless it was astronomically
through the roof and you're like a super
sensitive responder, even that alone is
we don't cut test doses in half. We
titrate it down. But based on the idea
that estrogen was too high, I mean,
that's yeah, you you need a new doctor.
It it's very I I I really disagree with
the idea that people should ignore what
their doctor said and get advice online.
the what people need to do is go the
advice online is saying my doctor's
wrong and I need to find another doctor.
You need to find a doctor who gives you
correct advice. So that's a big red
flag. Um especially given that you feel
like garbage. I mean you you did it and
it didn't work out for you, which
doesn't surprise me, but um yeah, find a
new doctor. Don't don't take advice
online about how you should change your
protocol. The only answer to this
question, find a new doctor. And as I
said, all the clinics attached to this
group, I mean, this this group has
aggregated, you know, all the best
providers in the US and we've got
connections to other providers outside
of the US. So when in doubt, I mean, one
of the things that's sad is when I log
into the Facebook group and see all
these posts, I'm like, all of these
issues could be presented if you just
went to one of the clinics attached to
this Facebook group. So um yeah the the
skill of the provider is the biggest
variable in the outcome of your
treatment followed by how well you look
after yourself.
>> So get a better provider.